# Talita Iza Nurazmi

Surabaya, Indonesia • +62 82251718018 • talitazmiza@gmail.com • https://www.linkedin.com/in/talita-iza-nurazmi/

## **SUMMARY**

Front-End Developer experienced in collaborating with Back-End Developers and Web Designers to improve usability. Enjoy working with team members to collaborate on fast delivery. Advanced and highly interested in Tailwind CSS and React.js, with additional knowledge of UI/UX.

### **EDUCATIONS**

Electronic Engineering Polytechnic Institute of Surabaya (EEPIS), Surabaya Bachelor's Degree, Informatics Engineering	Oct 2022 – Mar 2024
Electronic Engineering Polytechnic Institute of Surabaya (EEPIS), Surabaya Associate's Degree, Informatics Engineering	Aug 2018 – Oct 2021

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

<ul> <li>Winning of Funding for Vocational Student Entrepreneurship Program</li> </ul>	2021
• EEPIS TEFL with score 453	2021
<ul> <li>1st Winner of Software Expo Department of Computer Informatics Engineering EEPIS</li> </ul>	2020

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

## **Softbridge.id**, Sidoarjo

Jun 2022 – Mar 2023

### **Programmer**

- Develop a CRM system for food companies (to improve business relationships) using Angular, Laravel, and Flutter.
- Compared data between the original data and the data entered into the system.
- Collaboration with data analysts for R&D of data that is requested in the system.
- Help Back-End Developers with coding and troubleshooting.
- Analyzed business needs by collaborating with stakeholders and users.
- Help Software Tester test some modules.
- Train users by division on how to use the system (marketing, finance, accounting, and production division).

# Ikatan Dokter Indonesia Wilayah Jawa Timur, Surabaya

Dec 2021 – Jan 2022

### Office Administrator

- Carry out secretarial activities (data recapitulation, making reminders, and holding a meeting for daily online meeting events).
- Designed daily posters for online meeting events.
- Make the opening video of the annual big event.
- Participate as a committee in the big annual event of Ikatan Dokter Indonesia Wilayah Jawa Timur as an event section and work as a team to ensure the event runs smoothly.
- Assist stakeholders and developers in gathering business requirements for new applications.

## PT PLN Rayon Krian, Krian

Jan 2020 - Feb 2020

## **Front-End Developer Intern**

- Develop a FAQ website with Laravel.
- Worked with users to understand business needs and convert those needs into actionable reports.

### **ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCES**

## Informatics Major Organizations, Surabaya

Nov 2018 - Jan 2021

## **Domestic Department Staff**

- Recapitulation of student attendance in Informatics EEPIS class 2015 2019.
- Submit a warning letter from management for students about alpha absence.
- Be in charge of the Ministry of Home Affairs program "Ramadan Nights 2019" as the chief executive
- Conduct a fundraising program (condolence news or achievement donations) in active classes.

## PKKMB EEPIS 2019, Surabaya

Aug 2019

### **Standby Team**

- Discipline new students during the PKKMB period.
- Help new students who are not physically fit and escort them to the Medical Team section, and accompany new students to move to their rooms.

## KMIPN 2018, Surabaya

Nov 2018

#### **Liaison Officer**

• Become a guide for participants, pick up and escort participants to the event room, and manage the participants' time according to the schedule.

## Share Happiness For Humanity, Surabaya

Apr 2017 – Aug 2017

#### **Human Resources**

• Gathering new members according to the target, helping with fundraising events, and providing general knowledge regarding the organization to the general public.

## **SKILLS**

#### Hard Skills:

- CRM
- Front-End Development (React.js, Vue.js, Angular)
- Back-End Development (Node.js Express.js, Laravel)

- REST APIs
- Adobe (Premiere Pro, Photoshop, Lightroom)
- Figma

#### **Soft Skills:**

- Team-oriented Attitude
- Adaptability
- Interpersonal Problem Solver

- Friendly and Positive Communicator
- Flexibility

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATIONS

**Projects**: EEPIS Online Library, Point of Sales for restaurant and retail, Urhealth for health app checker, FAQ with Laravel, UI/UX design for midwife app, MiPortafolio for personal portfolio.

**Certifications**: Certificate Complete React Bootcamp (Udemy), Data Wrangling Python (DQLab), Belajar Machine Learning untuk Pemula Certificate (Dicoding Indonesia).